girl you look like you must be a K pop fan wow how'd you know
if I give you this digi cam can you show me what K pop
summer looks like for you sure
who do you feel was everywhere on your for you page this summer
I think Ateez I saw them literally
all over my for you page the audio was being used everywhere
definitely BTS I always feel excited what's revealed on each
there were so many k pop trends this summer
which ones were your favorite I really love dance challenges
specifically Red Red Bad by 80s was amazing so
I just love being able to see everyone following along with the trend
what do you think has made the summer so K pop
I think it's how global K pop has
become there's just so many more opportunities to see idols in person
is there an artist that you discovered because of TikTok this summer
I think Kiki for sure I think a lot of their music is very
girl pop Summer Coated was there a K pop
trend you kept seeing all over your for you page this summer the rude
challenge where it was Dallas part in the middle
where she's like you know what he said to me what
he was like you're so rude